[{"answer": "You'll to have to ask him.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say any incriminating things that are going to make it harder to kind of make peace.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "I want my $200!", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Will you quiet down, you hear?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "I'm well.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Tatum, how are you?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, I've always thought you were a part of our family.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Do you have an overwhelming sense of relief, both of you, do you think, that at least you've managed to get back to somewhere even if it's not perfect yet?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "I felt like I would be there for him because it's Father's Day and it's the day our show launches and it seemed like the right thing to do.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "How did you feel when he asked you over for Father's Day?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Have you watched it together yet?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "I don't really think about that.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "When you see that little girl in \"Paper Moon\" -- a role that changed your life -- when you see that, do you wish sometimes you'd never been pushed into that world?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Of course and \"What's Up Doc?\"", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Do you ever -- do you still watch it every now and again?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, with my daughter.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Let's focus on you.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "About him?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "About me?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "I would say 98 percent.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "How much have the drugs played a part in the downside of your life?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "They were around.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "How did you get them?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "People's houses.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "People's houses?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "First pot, then Quaaludes, I think, and then -- first alcohol actually, and then, you know, it just led on and on.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "And what was the drug?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "You'll have to ask him.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say any incriminating things that are going to make it harder to kind of make peace and have a healing.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Well, obviously like you showed, the arrest, that was terrible.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What have been your worst moments involving drugs when you look back, the ones where you felt most ashamed?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Through a friend, a person, after my divorce.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "How did you get to heroin?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "'NEAL: No.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Still call him friend?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I feel good about myself.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "When you look at yourself now, what do you see and what do you think?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Thank you for saying that.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "I thought, well, this is a very attractive, normal-looking woman, how can this be the crazy Tatum O'Neal?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I know I'm winning the battle.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Do you think you're winning the battle?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I've been sober for a year now.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "How long have you been clean now?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Like beyond.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "And are you proud of that, yourself?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Do you recognize that kind of self-destruct button?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "There are so many different ways now.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "What's the best way for any addict to try and deal with it once this has all been blown up like it has?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "For me, a 12-step program worked for me.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "What did you find was the best way?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I know it's saving my life a day at a time, for sure.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Did it save your life, do you think?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Amazing.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "How do you physically feel these days?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Not even -- not even a little bit.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Do you miss drugs?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I'm grateful.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Are you surprised at that?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I felt the sense of abandonment.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "And did you feel not a sense of abandonment but something like that?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Did you ever get mad at her?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "She was one of the most beautiful women in the world, of course.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "And I was sort of like, you know, looking at her pictures and thinking, gosh, you know, how I am going to kind of compete?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Just that one that I write about in my book, where I went to talk to her while she knew she was sick in her apartment, and got to kind of talk to her.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Did you have any real relationship with her for a long time?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Was she sorry to you for what had happened?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Well, I think so.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Do you think she was the love of your dad's life?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Well, if you know my dad, and you'll get to meet him, you'll sort of see that he is just always joking and stuff.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Is he basically just an incurable romantic, do you think, your dad?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "You're so right.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "He loves women?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "It was fun.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What was it like walking around with Ryan O'Neal after \"Love Story\"?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "I did some fun things with my ex-husband as well.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "What was the most exciting thing you ever did, when you look back at it, wow?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Yes, and nice, gosh, he was so nice.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Was he any good, George?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Good tennis player?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Well, he was sort of giving a little lesson to Ben, his son, who is now grown.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "He even destroyed George Harrison's game?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "So far I honestly would have to say Oprah.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Who left the biggest impression on you?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I would have, but I think I was...", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Listen, when I saw him with the Faces, it was 1975.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "You must be offended, aren't you?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "He was taking me to the car because I was sleeping because I was 11.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Where was he taking you?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I'm not really sure.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Why do you think that it never really happened in the way it should have done?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "I wouldn't tell you, because they're my suspicions, so I'm not going to say it on national television.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "What are you suspicions?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "'NEAL: I think I would like to be working in a way that was just where I would be considered kind of thing.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Would you like to be in a movie again?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Well, for -- I think people are wary.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Do you get offers at the moment, or are people still a little wary?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I would totally employ myself.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Would you employ yourself right now?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Oh, I get a lot of women saying, we love you, Tatum.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "When you walk around, what reaction do you get from the public these days?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Are you on Twitter?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, I will now.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "You're not following me?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "@Tatum_Oneal.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "What's your address?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "I'm Don Lemon live in New York.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "And when come back, I want to ask you on that same theme, really, do you think you're going to live happily ever after now?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Twenty-two.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Well, do you know how old I was when I married him?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "We get on as well as a divorced couple who have three grown kids can.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "How do you get on these days?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Do you talk regularly?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "Do you talk to your ex-wife regularly?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Maybe two.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Six years ago?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Two years ago?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "Mine.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "Whose decision was it to end the marriage?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "Not well.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "How did he take that?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't have any love life.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "What's your love life like these days?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Zero.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Zero?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "No, I'm really not.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "Are you looking for a man?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "Maybe a gentle, smart, loving person.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "What kind of man do you think now you ought to be with?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "Wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110619pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 758}]